# Tom Shaffir

# **Angular developer**

tom.shaffir@gmail.com



053-3320-792

ın

https://www.linkedin.com/in/tom-shaffir-a36289125



Tel-Aviv

24/10/1987



https://tomshaffir.github.io/tom-portfolio

## **EXECUTIVE SUMMARY**

A software development and performance engineering with 3 years of experience in the high-tech manufacturing and Internet industries. Strong analytical abilities, questioning mind and critical thinking, fast learner - quickly fits in, team player with great interpersonal skills, **changing position** towards FRONT-END developing, in particular ANGULAR 2+

#### **EDUCATION**

2017 - 2018 Certificate: Angular 2+, JavaScript from Coursera and more (140+ Hours)

2012 - 2016 B.sc. in COMPUTER SCIENCE; Tel Hai College (GPA score: 85), Psychometric score: 720

2003 - 2006 Full matriculation; Math, Physics, English (5 Units), Emek High School (score: 106)

### FRONT END PROFESSIONAL COURSES

Deeply learning & Hands-on Projects building on the following topics:

Angular 2+, Css 3, Javascript, Es5/Es6, Redux (basic), TypeScript, Bootstrap, Html 5, Angular styling & animations, Advanced Rxjs library

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## 2015-2017 Mellanox technologies, Linux drivers developer

- R&D team, Researching & Developing complex data traffic abilities (Infiniband).
- Drivers coding (Infiniband) on both C & Assembly.
- Using Scrum work method as a Team standard.
- Verifies items created or defined by developing and conducting tests (Python mainely).
- Consistently met deadlines for key projects before tape-out.
- Coordinates with hardware design engineers to provide effective system solutions.
- Increased revenue by assuming more projects and diligently completing all required tasks.
- Experience in Linux embedded systems development, Linux OS internals, with real time schedulers, multi-threaded programming and inter-process communications in Linux OS environment.

## 2014-2015 Vision Systems, RT embedded (student job)

- A student job assigned to RT embedded team.
- Hard real time developing for a navigation device.

## 2013 Computer science preparatory, Tel-Hai college, Teacher assistant

- Teaching introduction to computer science, 5 level mathematics and Assembly.
- Frontal teaching both groups & individuals.

## **MILITARY SERVICE**

2006-2011 RANK: Officer captain (3 stripes). Permanent service as intelligence officer in Unit 76.

### **TECHNOLOGIES & CODING**

C, Assembly, Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, Firebase, Git, TCP/IP, OSPF, STP, IGMP, AWS and more.

#### LANGUAGES

Hebrew - Primary Language | English - High Level